(...ii-it might've very well...
...two one zero. Variable two one zero
...ask me that question. I just can't answer it.
...)
And you evade him
You evade him
But one of these days
And I shall care for you he is gonna nail you
Right on the chin and down they go
(...)
I was a liar
When I said
I am not afraid
I am
Born in the blood, born in the blood
Every brick and tile
Every inch of land and sky
Now to the almighty bank
Bow I
Born in the blood, born in the blood
Every dream I held aloft
And every thought I thought
Was mine
Is bought and sold and sold again
Back to me
Born in the blood, born in the blood
Every quieter voice
Is lost under
The white noise
They're old enough to hold a gun
The ones who don't remember
We were born in the blood
Born in the blood, born in the blood
To the slow dance of
A heavy tide we must abide
Towards the limestone towards the lime
To the slow dance of
A heavy tide we must abide
Towards the limestone towards the lime
Into the teeth of time